Guide to the Duke Student Government Records, 1960-2019 UA.31.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA 2003-0041, 1966-2003, 10 boxes
  - Conference on Career Choices, 1994 (Box 9)
  - University Committee on Diversity, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Inauguration (DSG), 1994 (Box 9)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Vice-President for Community Interaction, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Executive Vice-President, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Vice-President for Facilities and Environment, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Vice-President for Academic Affairs, 1994 (Box 9)
  - DSG Judiciary, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - DSG Vice-Presidents, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - DUSDAC, 1994 (Box 9)
  - University Union, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Chronicle Advertising / Community Calendar, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Report of Student Affairs Trustee Committee, undated (Box 9)
  - Task Force Planning New Residence Halls, Residence College, and East Campus, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Report of Residential Policy Committee--Subcommittee on Commitment-Houses, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Residential Programming Progress Report, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Town Meeting, 1993 (Box 9)
  - ASDU Responses to the New Living Option Task Force Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Task Force on a New Living Option--Subcommittee on Location- Renovations-Dining, 1985 (Box 9)
  - New Living Option Task Force Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 9)
  - Task Force on a New Living Option--Subcommittee on Freshmen, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Task Force on New Living Option--Subcommittee on Student Selection, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Towerview Dormitory, circa 1986 (Box 9)
  - Room rent comparisons to other institutions, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Housing Lottery (Rising Sophomore Placement): Memo from Wannamaker RAs, 1984 (Box 9)
  - East Campus, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Residential Life, 1994 (Box 9)
  - East Campus / Residential Planning, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Housing members, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Residential Plan Committee, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Trinity Park Association, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Residential Housing, 1996 (Box 9)
  - DSG Constitution, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Trustee Luncheon, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Committee appointments, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - Committees, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Search Committee Dean & Faculty, undated (Box 9)
  - DSG Legislature, 2002-2003 Session, Agendas and Minutes, 2002 Sept. 25-2003 Apr. 16, 15 folders (Box 9)
  - LIP Proposals, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Executive Files, 2001-2003 (Box 9)
  - Financial Aid Task Force Report and supporting documents, 2001-2002, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Developmental Senior Survey, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Faculty Associates Program, 1995 Sept. (Box 9)
  - Residential Life Report, 1996 June (Box 9)
  - University Alcohol Policy, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Selective House Policy, 1997 Feb. (Box 9)
  - "Duke University in an Interdependent World," 1994 Nov. 19 (Box 9)
  - Duke University Interfraternity Council, Board of Advisors Meeting, 1995 May 20 (Box 9)
  - Shaping Our Future, Shaping Our Present: A Progress Report on Duke University's Long Range Plan, Confidential, 1995 Nov. 27 (Box 10)
  - Wake Forest University Student Government Mid-Year Report, 1991-1992 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee: Agenda and Supporting Documents, 1996. Sept. 27 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee: Agenda and Supporting Documents, 1997 May (Box 10)
  - Board of Trustees Student Affairs Agenda, 1995 Sept. 29 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee: Agenda and Supporting Documents, 1966 May 10 (Box 10)
  - Plan for the Enhancement of Residential Life and Co-curricular life, 1994 Dec. 10 (Box 10)
  - Board of Trustees Student Affairs Agenda, 1993 Feb. 26 (Box 10)
  - Jeri Powell, V.P., Facilities and Athletics--Agendas, 1992-1998, and DSG Retreat, 1996 Sept. 21, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Medical Center Construction / PGI Replacement, undated (Box 10)
  - Facilities and Athletics (university committee)--surveys, parking, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Bryan Center, undated (Box 10)
  - Committee on Facilities and Environment (CFE), 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Legislative Retreat, 2002 (Box 10)
  - DSG mailing lists, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Letters--Duke admin. to various DSG members, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Student Groups, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Faculty Associates Program, 1995-2000 (Box 10)
  - Summary of DSG Accounts, undated (Box 10)
  - First Priority, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Selective House Presidents, 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Mid-Semester Evaluations for Jasmin French, circa 2000 (Box 10)
  - Event Evaluation, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Undergraduate Enrollment, 1997-1998 (Box 10)
  - Timothy Lomperis tenure controversy--articles, 1993-1994 (Box 10)
  - Legislative Agendas, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Alcohol Policy Review Committee, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Committee Info, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Legislative Agendas, 2000-2001 Session, 2000 Sept. 20-2001 Apr. 4, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Legislative Retreat, 2000-2001 Session (Box 10)
  - Major Projects, 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - DTV Movie Channel, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Breast Cancer Walk-a-thon, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Mayor Tennyson, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Semester Evaluations, undated (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Committee Agenda, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Devil's Desires, 1999 (Box 10)
  - DSG in the Chronicle, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Equal Pay Day, Alcohol Forums, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - DSG Legislator Declaration of Candidacy, 1997, 2001, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1998 (Box 10)
  - DSG "12th Man" Contest applications, undated (Box 10)
  - Scavenger Hunt--main folder, past sponsors, packets, Chronicle ads, helpful hints, and thank-you letters, 1989-1993, 6 folders (Box 10)
  - Bianca Motley: VP Student Affairs, 1996-1998, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 10)
  - Student Affairs Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 10)
  - Service Activities Points Distributions, undated (Box 10)
  - "Report to the President," by William H. Willimon, Dean of the Chapel, 2000 Nov. (Box 10)
  - DSG A to Z, 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Committee Agendas, 2000-2001 (Box 10)
  - Political Stances, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Community Service Center (CSC)--agendas, budgets, constitution, membership, memos, minutes, restructuring, and other information, 1992-1993, 8 folders (Box 10)
  - Race Relations, 1977-1995 (Box 10)
  - Durham Education, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Student Trustee, undated (Box 10)
  - ACC Leadership Conference, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Affordable Housing Loan, 1989, 1992, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Brightleaf Project, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Black Faculty Initiative, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Scope!, 1993 (Box 10)
  - ECASU, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1993 (Box 10)
  - Old House Rules, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Parliamentary procedure, undated (Box 11)
  - Administrator packets, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Advertising, 1993 (Box 11)
  - DSG files, 2002-2003 (Box 11)
  - Financial aid brochure, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Financial Aid Survey Results, undated (Box 11)
  - Financial Aid Task Force, 1999-2000 (Box 11)
  - Inside ASDU, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Election Packet, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Election numbers, 1997-1998 (Box 11)
  - Discover DSG, 1993-1997, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Housing Numbers, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - ASDU Legislative Guides, 1987-1992 (Box 11)
  - LIP Forms, General SOFC and DSG information, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - DSG Guides and Info, undated (Box 11)
  - Executive VP, DSG--correspondence, out (Randy Fink), 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Goals for VP's Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Goals of Past VP's, 1992-1994 (Box 11)
  - Evaluations, Fall 1995 (Box 11)
  - FATF Information, 2001-2002 (Box 11)
  - DSG Goals, 1994-1995 (Box 11)
  - Sub-Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Appointments--Committee lists/appointments (current), 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Process bylaws, appointment guidelines, responsibilities, 1995 (Box 11)
  - University Committees, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Currently-recognized groups, 1996 May (Box 11)
  - Clubs and Organizations, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Rosters, 1993-1996, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Orientation packs, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Orientation packet, Duke Bill of Rights, undated (Box 11)
  - DSG Community Interaction Committee (CIC), 1999-2000, 11 folders (Box 11)
    Meetings, surveys, study of alcohol policy on campus, and the group's "Final Report, 1999-2000."
  - "Assessment Report: Student Life at Duke," undated (Box 11)
  - Young Trustee Nominating Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 11)
  - DSG Legislative Retreat, 2000-2001 (Box 11)
  - Intercommunity Council, undated (Box 11)
  - Halloween Fun Packet, undated (Box 11)
  - Casino Night Organizing Committee, 1995 (Box 11)
  - Black Cultural Center, UNC-CH, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Union Constitution, 1999 (Box 11)
  - DSG from A to Z, 1999-2000 (Box 11)
  - Student Alcohol Information Committee, Fall 2000 (Box 11)
  - Asianation Membership Packet, 2000-2001 (Box 11)
  - Community Interaction Comm. Agenda & Notes, 2000 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Community Interaction Comm. Agenda, 1999 Sept. 20 (Box 11)
  - Chronicle Scavenger Hunt, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Spectrum Constitution, undated (Box 11)
  - DSG Legislature House Rules, undated (Box 11)
  - Bryan Center, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Bryan Center (BC) Walkway Proposal, undated (Box 11)
  - Office of Intercultural Affairs, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Multicultural Student Affairs, 2001, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - University Committees, circa 1997 (Box 11)
  - Points Authorization Form, 1995 (Box 11)
  - At-Large Reps, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Agendas--Executive and Cabinet, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Board Report, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Resolutions and Statutes, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Random, 1995-1997 (Box 11)
  - Legislative assistant, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Election information, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Housing numbers, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Sarah Mitchell, Executive VP, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Legislator Individual Projects (LIPs), 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - LIPs, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Financial Aid Report Part 2, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Financial Aid Committee goals, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
  - FATF crosstabs, 2001 (Box 12)
  - FATF emails, 2002 (Box 12)
  - FATF Survey II Draft, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Financial aid--Federal info, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Retreat info, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - Calendars, 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Campus representatives, 1995-1997, 8 folders (Box 12)
  - Car policy analysis, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Advisory Committee on Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 12)
  - By-laws (current and old), 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Correspondence, Executive Vice-President, 1992-1997, 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Correspondence of the Legislature, 1996 (Box 12)
  - DSG Cabinet, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
  - DUFSAC, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Fundraising efforts, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Issues and topics, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee (SHAC), 1995 (Box 12)
  - Standing committee members, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
- Accession UA 2005-0052, 1970-2005, 7 boxes
  Covers a wide variety of topics, with no one area predominating. Although almost all materials date from the late 1990s and early 2000s, this accession also contains the oldest item in the collection, an early 1970s scrapbook of ASDU history. Arranged as received.
  - DSG Cabinet (training), 1999-2003 (Box 12)
  - Curriculum 2000 Review Committee, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Academic Affairs, 2003-2004 (Box 12)
  - BAA, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Community Standard, 2003 (Box 12)
  - SACES, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Library Council, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Dean's Excuse, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Grade inflation, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Alcohol policy, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Archives, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Dean Chafe, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - By-Laws to revisit, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Joe Pietrantoni, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Greek Leadership and Life, 1995, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Event policy, 2000 (Box 12)
  - DSG and ASDU history, circa 1993 (Box 12)
  - DSG Executive Board, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
  - Recommendations to the President Concerning Cultural Space, 2001 Apr. 25 (Box 12)
  - Residential Life, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Reservations, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Community Service Initiative, 1998 (Box 12)
  - CITIE Steering Committee, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Party monitors, 2001-2002 (Box 12)
  - PACOR, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Faculty Associates Program, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Black faculty, 1988-1994, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - "A Color-Coded Guide to Campus Living Groups," prepared by Adrianne G. Threatt, Summer 1992 (Box 12)
  - Young Trustee Nominating Committee--guidelines and timelines, 1998, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Loose materials, 2000-2004, 2 folders (Box 13)
    Unarranged materials found loose in the box; topics in these materials include miscellaneous DSG agendas and minutes, C2K review, and plans for library renovation and consolidation.
  - PACOR, 1995-1996, 6 folders (Box 13)
  - Chapel Unions, 1997-2000 (Box 13)
  - Current projects, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Committee Report: Review of the Organization and Function of the Pre-major Advising Center, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Annual Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - New groups--charter and recognition requests (approved), 2003-2004 (Box 13)
  - Budget copies, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - Budget, 2001-2002, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - DSG, A to Z, 2003-2004 (Box 13)
  - Student Funding Task Force, 2002-2003 (Box 13)
  - SOFC Organization List, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Programming Fund requests (approved), 2003-2004, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - SOFC Budgets, 2001-2002 (Box 13)
  - DSG Legislative Retreat, 2003 (Box 13)
  - DSG Election violation case, 2003 (Box 13)
  - DSG Senate, Tenth--agendas, 2003-2004 (Box 13)
  - Union Chairs, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - University Life memos and info, 1998 (Box 13)
  - UJB appointees, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Special Events and Conference Services, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Send-Home Chronicle ad, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Fall and spring club allocations, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Certificates of appreciation, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Catering, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Car rental info, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - DSG Audit, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Alcohol policy, 1997-2002 (Box 13)
  - SCOPE, 1998 Mar. 6-8 (Box 13)
  - Room reservations--contacts and policies, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Student Affairs--strategic plan updates, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - "Building Academic Community: a Plan for University Residential Life," 1998 (Box 13)
  - University committees, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Committees--applications, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Random DSG Stuff, 1996-1998 (Box 14)
  - Related DSG Stuff, 1994-1997 (Box 14)
  - Letters to admin. and faculty, introduction and invite to mixer, 1994-1999 (Box 14)
  - Legislative packet given out during training, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - VP Staff Briefing Papers, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Cabinet, 2001-2004, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Summer Advisory Group, 1995-2001, 6 folders (Box 14)
  - Martin Pulido--EAC, undated (Box 14)
  - Judith White, 2001 (Box 14)
  - President's Office (Nan Keohane), 2001 (Box 14)
  - African and Afro-American Studies Program, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - DSG End of Year Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Canned Food Drive, circa 2003 (Box 14)
  - STRETCH Conference, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Duke LEADS, 2003 (Box 14)
  - IT Portal Master Calendar, 2003 (Box 14)
  - DSG Summer Executive Retreat, 2003 (Box 14)
  - DSG Summer Advisory meetings, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Duke University Union, mission and constitution, 2002 (Box 14)
  - DSG and GPSC student orientation for the Board of Trustees Standing Committees, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Executive meeting documents, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Recent DSG documents, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Election documents, Clifford Yu Davidson, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Trustee Standing Committee appointees, 1993-1998 (Box 14)
  - Election receipts, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Expenditures, FY 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - Off-campus security and responsibility, 1997 (Box 14)
  - The Agenda (DSG newsletter), 1997 Apr. (Box 14)
  - Mail service survey, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Line policy, 1994 (Box 14)
  - DSG depreciation schedules, 1992-1997 (Box 14)
  - Treasurer--miscellaneous papers, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - New office space--plans and funding, 1994 (Box 14)
    Contains blueprints.
  - Legislature--house rules and other information, 1993-1999 (Box 14)
  - Duke Greeks, undated (Box 14)
  - DSG stationery and logo, undated (Box 14)
  - DSG officers, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Young Trustee application materials, 1977, 1997 (Box 14)
  - Invoices, 1997-1998 (Box 14)
  - Election certifications, 2001-2002 (Box 14)
  - Candidacy declarations, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Campaign budgets, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Class officer certifications, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Compliance by-law forms, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Election certifications, Spring 2003 (Box 14)
  - Questionnaires, declarations, and petitions, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Candidacy declarations, 2003-2004, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Completed At-Large applications, 2003-2004, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Candidate declarations and compliance forms, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - Candidate declarations--class officers, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - President--declarations and petitions, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - VP of Academic Affairs--declarations and petitions, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - VP of Community Interaction--declarations and petitions, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - Budget proposals (campaigns), undated (Box 15)
  - Candidate petitions (East), undated (Box 15)
  - Visions--data responses and survey results, 2003 (Box 15)
  - ACC Leadership, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - DSG Legislature, 2001-2002 Session, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Election documents, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - Facilities and Athletics, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - FMD Holiday Food Drive, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - SOFC requests, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - Advising at Duke University--Moneta class documents, 2002, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Committee for Facility and Athletic Affairs, 2002-2003, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Duke University Athletic Council, 2002 Oct. 26 (Box 15)
  - Duke University Environmental Management Advisory Council (DUEMAC), 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Facilities and Athletics--safety, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Washington Duke Inn & Golf Club--proposed hotel upgrade and expansion, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - DSG Executive Retreat, 2002 (Box 15)
  - Various committees (LIPs, Academic Affairs, Student Affairs, Facilities and Athletics, and Community Interaction), undated, Disbound unlabeled binder (Box 16)
  - DSG questionnaire sponsored by Student Affairs Committee, circa 2000-2001, 3 folders (Box 16)
    Approximately 600 completed questionnaires about DSG activities, found as loose materials.
  - DSG Legislature, 9th--notebooks of Cliff Davison, VP for Facility and Athletic Affairs, 2002-2003, 2 folders--disbound binder (Box 16)
  - Committee for Facility and Athletic Affairs--notebooks of Cliff Davison, VP for FAA, 2002-2003, 3 folders--disbound binder (Box 16)
  - Curriculum 2000--notebook, 2003, 2 folders (Box 16)
    Removed from unlabeled binder; materials appear to be a review of C2K.
  - Curriculum 2000--loose materials, 1997-2003, 2 folders (Box 16)
    Found loose, in and near the binder above; some materials may duplicate the binder, but others derive from earlier dates.
  - LIP Report forms, 1999-2000 (Box 16)
  - Online Voting, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Blue Devil Canned Food Drive, 2002 (Box 16)
  - At-Large questionnaires, 2003 (Box 16)
  - Budget, Election Compliance forms, 2003 (Box 16)
  - Candidate statements, 2003 (Box 16)
  - Campaign budgets, 2004 (Box 16)
  - Executive VP candidates, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - VP for Facilities and Athletics, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - VP of Student Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - DSG Legislative Retreat, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Joshua Jean-Baptiste, DSG VP for Student Affairs, 2001-2002, 2 folders--disbound binder (Box 16)
  - ACC Leadership Conference, 2002 (Box 16)
  - University and Trustee committee applications and membership, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
  - Club recognition requests, 2001-2002 (Box 16)
  - University committees, 2002-2003 (Box 16)
  - BOT/Presidential committees, 2002-2003 (Box 16)
  - University and Cultural Fund applications, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
  - DSG Undergraduate Task Force on Financial Aid, "Financial Aid Car Policy Analysis," 2002 (Box 16)
  - LIP Proposals, 2000-2001 (Box 17)
  - Report of the Student Alcohol Information Committee, 2000 (Box 17)
  - Proceedings: 1st Annual Unity Through Diversity Luncheon, "Our Binding American Experience," 2000 Nov. 7 (Box 17)
  - DSG--photocopied clippings from The Chronicle, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - PACOR, 1998-1999 (Box 17)
  - Residential Life History, 1992-2002 (Box 17)
  - Old by-laws, circa 1993 (Box 17)
  - Chronicle clippings--various campus issues, 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - DSG miscellaneous loose papers, circa 1993 (Box 17)
  - Two scrapbooks of news clippings, mainly from The Chronicle, documenting ASDU's history. Scrapbook I covers the early to mid-1970s, Scrapbook II the late 1980s. (Box 19)
  - Campus Master Plan 2000, spiral-bound oversize notebook, produced by the Office of the University Architect (Box 19)
- Accession UA 2008-0046, 2006-2007, 1 box
  Accession contains written memoranda, communications, and other documents generated mainly by DSG President Elliott Wolf and other executive board members of the 2006-2007 Duke Student Government. Materials cover the period April 2006-May 2007. Records include extensive discussions of the Campus Culture Initiative, the University's response to the 2006 "Lacrosse Incident," student input to the Board of Trustees, and interactions with Durham city officials concerning the rights of Duke undergraduates.
  - Summer update, 2006 (Box 17)
  - Fall update, 2006 (Box 17)
  - Memoranda to Judicial Affairs Review Board, 2007 (Box 17)
  - Memoranda to various Duke and Durham officials, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
  - Official reports and public statements, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
  - Memoranda and remarks by Elliott Wolf to the Board of Trustees, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    Conditions Governing Access
    RESTRICTED until 2057.
  - Spring update, 2007 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence with DSG officials and Duke administrators, 2006-2007
    Consists primarily of correspondence between Elliott Wolf, DSG President 2006-2007, and various DSG officers and Duke administrators.
    - Richard Brodhead, President, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    - John Burness, Senior VP for Public Affairs and Government Relations, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    - Kemel Dawkins, VP for Campus Services, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    - Joe Fore, DSG Executive VP, 2006-2007, 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Peter Lange, Provost, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    - Larry Moneta, VP for Student Affairs, 2006-2007, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Paul Slattery--DSG Chief of Staff, '06-'07, and DSG President, '07-'08, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    - Tallman Trask III, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
    - Jim Wulforst, Director of Dining Services, 2006-2007 (Box 17)
- Accession UA 2019-0048, 2014-2019
  Scope and Contents
  Accession includes meeting minutes from the Duke Student Government Senate for all years 2015-2019. For academic years 2016-2017 and 2017-2018, also included are Executive Board meeting minutes, annual budgets from the Student Organizations Finance Committee, documents from Affiliate Bodies, and General information, including rosters.
  - Duke Student Government 2015-2016, 2014-2018; 217 document (MS Word, MS PowerPoint, and PDF formats) files; approximately 60 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA31-02-0002-SET-0001)
  - Duke Student Government 2016-2017, 2016-2019; 264 document (MS Word, MS PowerPoint, and PDF formats) files; approximately 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA31-02-0002-SET-0001)
  - Duke Student Government 2017-2018, 2017-2019; 387 document (MS Word, MS PowerPoint, and PDF formats) files; approximately 125 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA31-02-0002-SET-0001)
  - Duke Student Government 2018-2019, 369 document (MS Word, MS PowerPoint, and PDF formats) files; approximately 160 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA31-02-0002-SET-0001)
- Accession UA 2019-0098, circa 2006